<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TextView</string>

    <string name="paragraph_name">Aim in Life</string>
    <string name="paragraph"> Everybody should have an aim or an ambition in life.  There are, however some persons who do not plan their careers.  They have no aim in life.

                \n \n Those who have no aim in life are like a ship without a rudder or an envelope without an address.  They are tossed to and fro by circumstances. They complain of hard times and
                blame their fate. It is no wonder that they cut a sorry figure in the battle of life.  While deciding our aim or choosing a career, we have to hope for the best and get prepared
                for the worst.  We must have some aim or ambition in life and should leave no stone unturned to achieve it.

                \n \n Different people have different aims.  Some persons want to become doctors while others want to start business.  If law appeals, to some, army has attraction for others.  Some aim
                at becoming a teacher while social service or politics attracts others.  So different people adopt different aims according to their inclination or taste or pocket.  It is the duty
                of the parents and the teachers to persuade their wards to choose a profession according to their aptitude.  Right aim means right life and wrong aim means a wrong life. So, we should
                be very cautions while deciding our aim.  Perhaps the most difficult problem that a young man faces is the choice of a profession.  If a person does not choose his aim rightly, he will
                be a square peg in a round hole.  The best profession would be one in which an individual feels at home and can do something worth- while and which, at the same time, assures him of
                good prospects in life.

                \n \n There are various professions.  I do not want to take a leap in the dark.  I know that success in life depends upon the well-planned aim.  Law and business may have charm for others,
                but they have no attraction for me.  Business needs a huge amount of money which I do not have.

                \n \n My aim, however, is to be a teacher.  Teaching is the noblest form of profession.  It is like killing two birds with one stone.  A teacher can earn an honest and independent living.
                He can serve his society and country in the best possible way.  He is a nation-builder.  He can mould the destiny, shape the future and can ennoble the minds of the students who are
                the wealth, pride and future of the country.  In a democracy where every adult is a voter, education is of utmost importance.  A teacher alone can impart the right type of education
                and make the students ideal citizens.  He can inculcate refined qualities in the young minds and create patriotic fervor in them.  If teachers are efficient and serve as torch-bearers
                to the students, our democracy will have a bright future.

                \n \n I know that teachers in these days are ill-paid and can hardly make both ends meet.  But money is not the only consideration with me.  He lives among the smiling faces and young hearts.
                So, he neither become old nor feels sad or serious.

                \n \n I will create a family atmosphere in the school and will teach my students as Gurus did in ancient times.  May God inspire me to be what I have decided to be!</string>
</resources>
